it is time for supreme splaining what you got for us a couple weeks ago when we had this topic
about pala what was a polygamy pala how do you say the other one pala amory i don't even want
to know polyamory and i noticed not one man called to say that he believed in this lifestyle
but i think i might be able to explain medically where this might be this might be a thing i mean
i'm not saying this for me but this might be a thing for somebody else let's hear what the good
doctor had to say there's a concept in physiology if you don't use it you lose it the study is
abundantly clear that a man should be able to have sexual interaction 21 times a month to avoid
prostate issues so yes you have a beautiful wife do whatever it takes to please that woman so she
can give it to you 21 times a month yeah hilarious so if she doesn't please you i advocate to my
patients that you can have a side check your side check will be on contract now i don't know what
this doctor's credentials are where he comes from but the man just prescribed other men side check i'm
not gonna argue with the science here doctor's orders when you get caught up just tell them it's
doctor's orders but don't let you honey
right